These subtitles are supplied by us, they should play in sync with the video.
They change in relation to the video play position, just like normal subs
This is the third srt chunk. It's funny, I guess this means we can add words of caution or correction
This guy seems chill.
The youtube supplied languages vary by video. Spanish is on almost all of them.
But with this, we can make curated lists with French, arabic, etc.
Of course I can only supply machine generated ones, but they can be revised and corrected.
Ok, now it's just going to repeat the same thing.
These subtitles are supplied by us, they should play in sync with the video.